{
    "id": "1210f5cb0aec4ff1b6f32d06c4ee54f2",
    "title": "Would Rather, Had Better, I Wish",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I would rather you ………………….. see her anymore.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "don't",
                "didn't"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "534ba77a889b49fa98a4fa2fce8496ac"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish I ……………….. speak Spanish.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "could"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "60c578558d0f4cd7bf21526aca8ad156"
        },
        {
            "question": "You had better ……………….. your ways.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "mended",
                "mend",
                "to mend"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4d7ff20b749045bea3382dc852bbe228"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish I ………………. to university.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have gone",
                "had gone"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "61b74b86faeb48788a480e5239b5aafb"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish tomorrow ……………. Sunday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "was"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "acc358b434d44fdf9abbc81d62537d83"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish you ………………. stop smoking.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "will"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1277ec7ac0294d72ab6490e94c662110"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish you …………………. be quiet.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1b5417b05df64d3ca05e1f3d7a5b90b4"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish it ………………… stop raining.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9b89fcdf19c64941932aa7c9f40be5f7"
        },
        {
            "question": "I would rather …………………. on the weekend.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to not work",
                "not work",
                "not to work"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f2ad6a2d1a4842f2abea31e429c6b63e"
        },
        {
            "question": "We had better ………………… for him or we will be late.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "not wait",
                "not to wait",
                "to not wait"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "13741d9c42f64f1599dc9c677c98ac25"
        }
    ]
}